https://www.powerlinesupplies.co.uk/privacy

The store will not work correctly in the case when cookies are disabled.
We use cookies to make your experience better.
To comply with the new e-Privacy directive, we need to ask for your consent to set the cookies.
Learn more.
Allow Cookies
Tattoo Machines Tattoo MachinesView all Tattoo MachinesCheyenne Hawk Tattoo MachinesAll Cheyenne Products Hawk PenHawk ThunderHawk SpiritHawk GripsBishop RotaryFK Irons Spektra Rotary LACEnanoStigma-Rotary®KillerBeeHM Tattoo Machine - Rotary Inkjecta Rotary MachineAll Rotary Tattoo MachinesSymbeos Rotary Tattoo MachineEgo Rotary MachineDragonfly Rotary MachineStingray Rotary MachineInvictus HM Rotary MachineRotary Works Rotary MachineRonnie Starr RotaryNedz Rotary Tattoo MachinesDormouse Equaliser Sunskin NeoTatLockHead PenSymbeos Rotary Tattoo MachineEikon Tattoo MachinesHM Manufacturing MachinesDragonfly Rotary Tattoo MachineStingray Rotary Tattoo MachineInkjecta Rotary Tattoo MachineInkjecta Flite V2.1Inkjecta GripsInkjecta Machine SparesEgo Rotary Tattoo MachineSabreRotary Works Tattoo MachineRonnie Starr Cast Tattoo MachinesRonnie Starr Fabricated MachinesNew York Irons Tattoo MachinesPirat Tattoo MachinesTattoo Machine PartsTattoo Machine SparesMachine Building ToolsMachine AccessoriesSpektra Rotary Tattoo MachineLauro PaoliniCoko Fernández Coil MachinesTattoo Power Supplies Tattoo Power SuppliesView all Tattoo Power SuppliesPower SuppliesFootswitchesClip CordsPower Supply AccessoriesTattoo Grips, Tips & Tubes Tattoo Grips, Tips & TubesView all Tattoo Grips, Tips & TubesSterile Disposable Tubes and TipsPowerline White Plastic Tattoo TubesPin Up Black Rubber Tattoo TubesCNC Seamless Tattoo TubesEikon Griffin Tattoo TubesDisposable Cartridge TubesPowerline White Plastic TipsCNC Seamless Long Plastic TipsCNC Short Plastic TipsAlla Prima Plastic TipsBlack Widow Tattoo TubesWrath Disposable TubesEGO Hawkflow Bishop RotaryBarber DTS TubesCheyenne Pen GripsTATSoul Wrath Recoil TubesTATSoul Wrath Foam TubesTATSoul Wrath Adjustable GripsStainless SteelStainless Steel Tattoo GripsStainless Steel Tattoo TipsAlla Prima TipsCheyenne Hawk GripsGrip And Tip AccessoriesAcetol And PlasticEgo BiogripsCoversTip AccessoriesCartridge Tubes and GripsTattoo Needles Tattoo NeedlesView all Tattoo NeedlesSterile Tattoo NeedlesPowerline Tattoo NeedlesPin Up Tattoo NeedlesCNC Tattoo NeedlesEikon Hydra Tattoo NeedlesMagic Moon Tattoo NeedlesNeedle GroupingsBlack Widow NeedlesBarber DTS Needles Envy Tattoo Needles Sabre Needles Enso Tattoo NeedlesTATSoul Big Sleeps NeedlesTATSoul Envy Gen 2 CartsBarber DTS CartridgesTATSoul Envy CartridgesPinUp Cartridges Da Vinci CartridgesCheyenne Hawk Needle CartridgesCheyenne Hawk Craft CartridgesPlatinium CartridgesLoose Needles And AccessoriesPowerpoint Loose NeedlesNeedle Making AccessoriesSabre Cartridges Sabre Shield Cartridges Elite Cartridges Elite 2 CartridgesPiranha Cartridges Tattoo Ink Tattoo InkView all Tattoo InkEternal InkEternal Basic Tattoo InksEternal Tattoo Ink SetsEternal Black And Greywash InksEternal Marshall Bennett GreywashEternal Zombie ColoursEternal Muted Earthtone ColoursEternal Portrait ColoursEternal Liz Cook ColoursEternal M Series ColoursEternal Seasonal Spectrum ColoursEternal Motor City ColoursEternal Jess Yen Colours Eternal Halo
- Fifth Dimension ColoursEternal Myke Chambers Colours Eternal Andrea Afferni ColoursEternal Rember Orellana Colours Eternal Sale Levgen Colours Frank La Natra Colours Four Colour Concentrate SetPerfect Storm By Mike DevriesBryan Sanchez Watercolour SetKelly Doty Resurrection Set Lyle Tuttle Colour SetEternal Big Gus Signature SeriesEternal Goran Micic ColoursWorld Famous InkWorld Famous Single Tattoo InksAlex Pancho Ink SetsMichele Turco Ink SetsOleg Shepelenko Ink Sets J. Ackerman Ink SetsMaster Mike Ink SetsSarah Miller Ink Sets Maks Kornev Ink SetsBig Joels Ink Sets Jay Freestyle Ink Sets Gorsky Ink Sets Poch Ink SetsCharcoal Greywash Sets Sticazzi Black SetsNuno Feio Pastel SetsJose Perez Sets5 Stage Shading SetsErich Rabel SetsRob Richardson SetsSilvano Fiato Sets Other World Famous Ink Sets Intenze InkIntenze Single Tattoo InksIntenze Tattoo Ink SetsIntenze Black And Greywash InksBob Tyrrell Black And Grey SetBoris from Hungary Color SetMario Barth Gold Label SetMike DeMasi Colour Portrait SetMark Mahoney Gangster Grey SetDragon Colour SetBowery Stan Ink SetColour Outline SetIntenze Earthtone SetRandy Engelhard ColoursAlex De Pase Colours Andy Engel ColoursNocturnal Ink Sea Shepherd by Quantum Tattoo InkBlack Tattoo InkDynamic Black InkPelikan InkObsidian Black InkTalens InkEternal Black InkIntenze Black InkKuro Sumi Black InkSilverback Black InkAlla Prima Black InkCheyenne Black InkMakkuro Sumi Black Ink MOMs InkMOMs Single Tattoo InksMOMs Tattoo Ink SetsMOMs Black And Greywash InksNuclear Black Light InksSkin Candy InkBloodline Tattoo InksSkincandy Neo Traditional InksSkin Candy Black And Greywash InksGreywash Tattoo InkEternal Greywash InkIntenze Greywash InkSilverback Greywash InkKuro Sumi Greywash InkSkin Candy Black And Greywash InksAlla Prima Greywash InkFormula 51 Greywash InkCheyenne Greywash InkRon Meyers Greywash InkMakkuro Sumi Greywash Ink Silverback InkSilverback Black And Greywash InksAlla Prima InkAlla Prima Single Tattoo InksAlla Prima Tattoo Ink SetsKuro Sumi InkKuro Sumi Colours Tattoo InksKuro Sumi Tattoo Ink SetsKuro Sumi Black And Greywash InksPanthera InkInk By ArtistBob Tyrrell Tattoo InksBoris from Hungary InksBowery Stan Moskowitz InksMike DeMasi InksMario Barth InksMark Mahoney InksM Series InksLiz Cook InksTattoo Ink AccessoriesMixing And Thinning SolutionsInk CapsInk Cap StandsBottles And ContainersImperial InksImperial Ink ColoursImperial Ink Greywash Viking InkFusion Tattoo InksFusion Colour RangeFusion Colour SetsFusion Pastel ColoursFusion Greywash ColoursFusion Flesh Tone ColoursFusion Ink Muted ColoursFusion Opaque Blue ColoursFusion Signature Pallette ColoursFusion Nikko Hurtardo ColoursFusion Juan Salgado ColoursFusion Roman Abrego ColoursFusion Jeff Gogue Pallette ColoursFusion Rick Walters ColoursFusion Deano Cook ColoursFusion Mike Cole ColoursSolid InkStandard ColoursStandard Colour SetsHoritomo Colour SetsBlack Label Grey Wash SetChris Garver SetBig Sleeps InkTattoo Shop Supplies Tattoo Shop SuppliesView all Tattoo Shop SuppliesFurnitureTatsoulOther FurnitureStencil Making And Art SuppliesSale Practice Skins And Body PartsTattoo Books And DVDsPaper ProductsStands And DisplaysBags, Bottles And CoversInk Caps, Stands And ThinnersClothing Tattoo Flash Designs Tattoo Flash DesignsView all Tattoo Flash DesignsTattoo Design SetsMatt LappingMike MastersMedical Tattoo Supplies Medical Tattoo SuppliesView all Medical Tattoo SuppliesDressing And TapesAnaesthetics And AntisepticsSurface, Floor And Couch CleaningSkin PreparationGloves, Protective Wear And Equipment CoversUltrasonics And AutoclavesTattoo And Piercing AftercareHand And Skin CleaningInstrument CleaningPiercing Supplies Piercing SuppliesView all Piercing SuppliesPiercing ProductsSterile Piercing NeedlesInstruments And ToolsPiercing AftercareNew Jewellery RangeBody JewelleryCNC Titanium Body JewelleryCNC Surgical Steel Body JewelleryDisposable Piercing Equipment Brands
CNC
Powerline
Pinup Tattoo Supplies
Eikon
Eternal Ink
Alla Prima
Kuro Sumi
Superbright Inks
Privacy & Security
Powerline Supplies is committed to respecting the privacy rights of visitors to its website. This privacy policy explains how we collect, store and use personal data about you when you browse or shop on our website.  It provides you with details about the types of personal data that we collect from you, how we use your personal data and the rights you have to control our use of your personal data.
You must read this privacy policy carefully and we recommend that you print and retain a copy for your future reference. By accessing, browsing or otherwise using this Website, you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to this privacy policy in its entirety.  If you do not agree to this privacy policy in its entirety, you must not use this Website.
Privacy Policy
We will treat all your Personal Information as confidential (although we reserve the right to disclose this information in the circumstances set out below). We will keep it on a secure server and we will fully comply with all applicable UK Data Protection and consumer legislation from time to time in place.
When you shop on this Website, we will collect Personal Information from you such as your name, e-mail address, billing address, delivery address and telephone number.  If you have registered with us we will also keep your user name and password together with your order history.  We may also collect information about where you are on the internet (eg the URL you came from, IP address, domain types like .co.uk and .com), your browser type, the country and telephone area code where your computer is located, the pages of our website that were viewed during your visit, the advertisements you clicked on, and any search terms that you entered on our website.  We may collect this information even if you do not register with us.
We confirm that any Personal Information which you provide to us (or which is available on public registers) and any User Information from which we can identify you, is held in accordance with the registration we have with the Data Commissioner's Office. We use your information only for the following purposes:
Processing your orders
For statistical or survey purposes to improve this Website and its services to you
To serve website content and advertisements to you
To administer this website;
If you consent, to notify you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you.
Marketing
When you order from this website you will be given the option to receive information from Powerline Tattoo Supplies about products, promotions or special offers which we feel may be of interest to you. In the event that you do not wish to be contacted for such purposes, ensure that you tick the appropriate box as you go through the ordering process. You may unsubscribe from our contact list at any time by replying to a promotional e-mail with the word "unsubscribe" which is at the bottom of the email,
Your Personal Information will only be disclosed to Powerline Supplies. and to reputable third parties who will help process your order. Powerline Supplies requires all such third parties to treat your personal information as fully confidential and to fully comply with all applicable UK Data Protection and consumer legislation from time to time in place. We will not release your Personal Information to any other company for mailing or marketing purposes.
Cookies
This Website uses cookies to collect information about you.  Cookies are small data files which are placed on your computer or other device by this Website and which collect certain personal data about you.  This enables us to tailor our service offering (including the Website) to provide you with products and services which are more relevant to your individual tastes.  You may change your website browser settings to reject cookies, although please note that if you do this it may impair the functionality of this Website.  For further information about cookies, including how to refuse cookies, please visit www.allaboutcookies.org.
This privacy notice does not cover the links within this site linking to other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit.
Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy. This privacy notice was last updated on 5th December 2011.
Questions regarding this Policy should be directed as follows:
Marketing Department,
Powerline Supplies,
Unit 25 Shortwood Court, Shortwood Business Park,
Dearne Valley Parkway,
Barnsley,
S74 9LH
